easyengine.io 2015-09-24

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy for rtCamp:**

  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own decision, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trademarks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of India or other regulatory authority.

 **Log Files:**  
rtCamp makes use of log files (which includes IP addresses, type of browser, internet service providers, referrer, number of clicks etc) to understand user movements and demographics. Such information is not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies:**

  * rtCamp use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
  * We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy. However we may use such information to update you about promotional offers and updates from us.

 **Support**

  * rtCamp gives support for premium products with Helpdesk. Helpdesk support requires raising a ticket on this website.
  * All personal data, admin information is accessible only to the user who raises the ticket and rtCamp’s support team.

 **Advertising:**

  * rtCamp has implemented and uses Display Advertising
  * rtCamp makes use of remarketing with Google Adwords and Google Analytics to advertise online
  * Our advertising campaigns don’t collect personally identifiable information (PII)
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet
  * rtCamp and third-party vendors, including Google, uses first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.
  * If you prefer ads not to be based on interests and demographics, then you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising using [Google Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/ "Google Ads Preferences Manager")

 **Changes in Our Privacy Policy:**  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or email us at contact@rtcamp.com as soon as possible.
